Guide to the Eastmont Human Services Center records 1960-2003
Montana Historical Society Research Center
Eastmont Human Services Center records
1960-2003
Montana Historical Society, Research Center Archives Archives 225 N. Roberts PO Box 201201 Helena MT 59620-1201 (406) 444-2681 mhslibrary@mt.gov
RS 463
Eastmont Human Services Center
45.4 linear feet of shelf space
This collection is comprised of records of the Eastmont Human Services Center and contains correspondence (1980-1999), subject files (1981-2004), meeting minutes (1980-1999), scrapbooks, photo albums and slides (1960-2003), and case files (1978-2003). MEDICAL RESTRICTION: Patient files are confidential and privileged (MCA 53-21-166 and MCA 50-16 part 5). For more information contact an archivist.
Administrative History
The Eastmont Human Services Center was established at Glendive in 1967 by the 40th Legislature. The center operated two facilities for lodging residents, a 40 bed cottage and a 15 bed cottage. The 15 bed cottage (Cottage II) originally housed residents under a five-day program where developmentally disabled students were bussed from the surrounding areas to the center for training classes during the week. Gradually, these students were integrated into the school system in their own communities.
By the 1980s, the purpose of the center was to provide residential and day training to people with severe developmental disabilities through an on-going seven-day program. The seven-day program includes people who range in age from fifteen to over sixty years. The majority of these residents transferred to the center from the Montana Developmental Center and required 24 hour supervision. Course instruction included academics, home living, perceptual training, social awareness, recreation and physical education, speech therapy, and pre-vocational training. Residents occupied fifty-two of the center's fifty-five beds at June 30, 1986.
The center closed in 2003 due to budget concerns. Authority was then transferred to the Montana State Department of Corrections where it was transformed into a DUI treatment center.
Content Description
This collection is composed of five series:
Correspondence (1980-1999) including incoming and outgoing correspondence organized chronologically by year. The folders were kept in their original order, which is roughly alphabetical. The folders are labeled by topic, department, or staff member.
Subject Files (1981-2004) including annual reports and director files.
Meeting Minutes (1980-1999) including the minutes and agendas for the numerous committee and staff meetings at the Eastmont Human Services Center.
Scrapbooks, Photo Albums, and Slides (1960-2003) including primarily photographs of patients, events, and activities that took place at the Eastmont Human Services Center.
Case Files (1978-2003) including patient’s identification information, social history and individual habilitation plans. This series is restricted.
This collection is arranged chronologically and/or alphabetically by series.
The majority of the collection is open to research with the exception of the patient records in the case files series. Patient files are confidential and privileged (MCA 53-21-166 and MCA 50-16 part 5). For more information contact an archivist.
Acquisition information available upon request
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the Montana Historical Society Archives catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search under these terms.
Health Care.; Institutional care-­Montana; Managed mental health care; Mental health facilities; Mental health services; Nursing.
Montana
Mental Health
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Correspondence
  - Accident Reports, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 1)
  - Department of Administration, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 2)
  - Construction and Maintenance, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 3)
  - Architecture and Engineering, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 4)
  - Advocacy Assistance, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 5)
  - Axel, Martin G., 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 6)
  - Bacon, Ruth E., 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 7)
  - Barthel, Rita, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 8)
  - Behavior Modification Programs, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 9)
  - Behavior Modification Plans, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 10)
  - Blouke, Peter (Dr.), 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 11)
  - Board of Institutions, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 12)
  - Board of Visitors, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 13)
  - Boulder River School and Hospital (BRSH), 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 14)
  - Brooks, Rich, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 15)
  - Brooks – Meal Count, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 16)
  - Brooks – Meal Serving Procedure, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 17)
  - Brooks – Menus, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 18)
  - Brooks – Food Service Work Schedule, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 19)
  - Butcher, Gerald F., 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 20)
  - Butcher – Budget, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 21)
  - Butcher – Executive Planning Process, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 22)
  - Butcher – Information from January, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 23)
  - Butcher – Maintenance Contracts Information, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 24)
  - Butcher – Memos – All Staff, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 25)
  - Butcher – MEA Union, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 26)
  - Butcher – MPEA Union, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 27)
  - Butcher – News Released, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 28)
  - Butcher – Pay Plan, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 29)
  - Butcher – Personnel Appeals, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 30)
  - Butcher – Speeches, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 31)
  - Calendars – School, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 32)
  - Christmas List, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 33)
  - Christmas Party, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 34)
  - Christmas Programs, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 35)
  - Community Affairs Department, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 36)
  - Conferences – Conventions, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 37)
  - Contracts, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 38)
  - Copy Machine Logs, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 39)
  - Council for Exceptional Children, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 40)
  - Department of Institutions, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 41)
  - Gooch, Thomas – Personnel Bureau, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 1 / 42)
  - Haubein, Jim, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 43)
  - Hoover, Jerry R., 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 44)
  - Hoffman, Ray, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 45)
  - Jessen, Barbara, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 46)
  - Kerr, Janie, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 47)
  - Language Therapist, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 48)
  - Powers, Philip, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 49)
  - Reimbursement, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 50)
  - Rotering, Nick – Attorney, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 51)
  - Zanto, Lawrence M., 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 52)
  - Degel, Peter J., 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 53)
  - Dawson County Mental Health Advisory Board, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 54)
  - Dawson Community College, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 55)
  - DD (Developmental Disabilities) Map, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 56)
  - Developmental Disabilities Planning and Analysis Committee (DDPAC), 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 57)
  - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 58)
  - Eastern Montana College, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 59)
  - Eastern Montana Industries, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 60)
  - Eastern Subarea Advisory Council, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 61)
  - Eastmont Parents Association, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 62)
  - Education Schedules, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 63)
  - Eide, Candace, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 64)
  - Emergency Building Temperature Restrictions (EBTR) Program, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 65)
  - Porter – Fire Drills, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 66)
  - Fox, William K., 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 67)
  - Judge – Governor, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 68)
  - Governance Committee Election Ballots, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 69)
  - Habilitation Review Schedule, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 70)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 71)
  - Holzer, Carol, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 72)
  - Education Component, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 73)
  - Jessen – Class Schedule Information, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 74)
  - Job Service, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 75)
  - Joint Commission, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 76)
  - Kramer, Judy, 1980 (Box-folder 1 / 77)
  - Kruger, Jan, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 1)
  - Larson, Dianne, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 2)
  - Law Suits, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 3)
  - Long Term Care Facility, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 4)
  - Low Priced Meals, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 5)
  - Mast, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 6)
  - Meal Schedules, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 7)
  - Developmental Services Department Meeting, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 8)
  - Molstad, Russ, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 9)
  - Noonan, Larry, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 10)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 11)
  - Paving Contract, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 12)
  - Personnel Audit Notes and Comments, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 13)
  - Porter, Chuck, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 14)
  - Postage Log, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 15)
  - Prison – Deer Lodge, MT, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 16)
  - RSUP, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 17)
  - Region I – Developmental Disabilities, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 18)
  - Region VIII – Developmental Disabilities, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 19)
  - Rodgers, Pamela, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 20)
  - Surveys, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 21)
  - School Year Calendars, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 22)
  - Senior Citizens Center, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 23)
  - Shanley, George, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 24)
  - Shodair Crippled Children’s Hospital, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 25)
  - Social and Rehabilitation Services (SRS) – Developmental Disabilities (DD) Division, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 26)
  - Surplus Property, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 27)
  - Surveys, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 28)
  - University of Alabama, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 29)
  - Weekly Schedule, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 30)
  - Van Schedules, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 31)
  - Waters, Debra, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 32)
  - Wright, Lorin; Hettinger, Joy, 1980 (Box-folder 2 / 33)
  - Department of Administration, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 34)
  - Architecture and Engineering Division, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 35)
  - Audit, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 36)
  - Bacon, Ruth E., 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 37)
  - Board of Institutions, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 38)
  - Board of Visitors, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 39)
  - Brooks, Richard E., 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 40)
  - Brooks – Food Service Forms, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 41)
  - Butcher – MEA, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 42)
  - Butcher – MPEA, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 43)
  - Butcher – All Staff Memos, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 44)
  - Butcher, Gerald F., 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 45)
  - Boulder River School and Hospital (BRSH), 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 46)
  - Butcher – Information – Accounting Tech, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 47)
  - Calendars, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 48)
  - Christmas Program, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 49)
  - Consolidation Information, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 50)
  - Contracts, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 51)
  - Department of Institutions, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 52)
  - Anderson, Dan, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 53)
  - Blouke, Peter (Dr.), 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 54)
  - Hoover, Jerry I., 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 55)
  - Kerr, Janie, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 56)
  - Powers, Phillip, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 57)
  - Rotering, Nick A., 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 58)
  - South, Carroll, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 59)
  - Zanto, Lawrence M., 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 60)
  - Degel, Peter J., 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 61)
  - Developmental Disabilities (DD) Map, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 62)
  - Developmental Disabilities Planning and Advisory Committee (DDPAC), 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 63)
  - Dawson Community College, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 64)
  - Department of Public Health and Human Services (DPHHS) – Region VIII, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 65)
  - Developmental Services Staff, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 66)
  - Eastern Montana Industries, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 67)
  - Eastern Subarea Advisory Council, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 68)
  - Governor’s Report, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 69)
  - Flesjer, Lilla, 1981 (Box-folder 2 / 70)
  - Grievance Committee, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 1)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 2)
  - Hoffman, Ray, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 3)
  - Huotari, Laurie, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 4)
  - In-Service Training – Food Services, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 5)
  - In-Service Training, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 6)
  - Individual Habilitation Plan (IHP) Schedules, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 7)
  - Inspections, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 8)
  - Interagency Committee, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 9)
  - Jessen, Barbara, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 10)
  - Jessen – All Staff Memos, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 11)
  - Class Scheduling Information, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 12)
  - Job Service, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 13)
  - Kruger, Jan, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 14)
  - Labor Relations, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 15)
  - Legislature, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 16)
  - Licenses, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 17)
  - Long Range Building Program, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 18)
  - McCallum – Title I, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 19)
  - Medicaid, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 20)
  - McKnight, Jacqueline, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 21)
  - Medicaid Reimbursement, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 22)
  - Molstad, Russ, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 23)
  - Montana Foundation for Medical Care, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 24)
  - Montana Health Systems Agency, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 25)
  - Montana Nursing Home Association, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 26)
  - National Association of Superintendents, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 27)
  - News Articles, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 28)
  - News Releases, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 29)
  - Noonan, Larry, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 30)
  - Office of Public Instructions, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 31)
  - Page, Dianne, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 32)
  - Police Department, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 33)
  - Porter, Charles L., 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 34)
  - Quotations, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 35)
  - Developmental Disabilities (DD) – Region VII, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 36)
  - Developmental Disabilities (DD) – Region I, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 37)
  - Rodgers, Pamela, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 38)
  - Social and Rehabilitative Services (SRS) – Developmental Disabilities (DD) Division, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 39)
  - Budget Forms, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 40)
  - Staffing Information, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 41)
  - Shanley, Cindy, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 42)
  - Studies, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 43)
  - Surveys, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 44)
  - Weekly Schedule, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 45)
  - Wright, L and Hettinger, J., 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 46)
  - Wurm, Jaci, 1981 (Box-folder 3 / 47)
  - Architecture and Engineering Division, 1982 (Box-folder 3 / 48)
  - Airline Schedules, 1982 (Box-folder 3 / 49)
  - Bacon, Ruth E., 1982 (Box-folder 3 / 50)
  - Biennium Report, 1982 (Box-folder 3 / 51)
  - Boese, Gail M., 1982 (Box-folder 3 / 52)
  - Boulder River School and Hospital (BRSH), 1982 (Box-folder 3 / 53)
  - Board of Visitors, 1982 (Box-folder 3 / 54)
  - Boiler Inspection Report, 1982 (Box-folder 3 / 55)
  - Brooks, Richard E., 1982 (Box-folder 3 / 56)
  - Budget Biennium, 1982 (Box-folder 3 / 57)
  - Butcher – Speeches, 1982 (Box-folder 3 / 58)
  - Butcher, Gerald F., 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 1)
  - Butcher – All Staff Memos, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 2)
  - Calendars, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 3)
  - Census, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 4)
  - Class Scheduling Information, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 5)
  - Conference Information, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 6)
  - Contracts, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 7)
  - Developmental Assessment Services (DAS), 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 8)
  - Department of Institutions, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 9)
  - Anderson, Dan, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 10)
  - Blouke, Peter J. (Dr.), 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 11)
  - Gooch, Tom, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 12)
  - Haubein, Jim, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 13)
  - Hoover, Jerry, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 14)
  - Kerr, Janie, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 15)
  - Powers, Philip, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 16)
  - Rotering, Nick A., 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 17)
  - South, Carroll V., 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 18)
  - Developmental Disabilities (DD) Map, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 19)
  - Developmental Success of Staff, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 20)
  - Eastern Montana Industry, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 21)
  - Eastmont Exchange, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 22)
  - Eastern Subarea Advisory Council, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 23)
  - Eastmont Parents Association, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 24)
  - Easter Seal Office of Public Instruction, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 25)
  - Fire Drills and Inspections, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 26)
  - Flesjer, Lilla, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 27)
  - Governor’s Report, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 28)
  - Gunderson, Kent, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 29)
  - Habilitation, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 30)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 31)
  - Help Wanted Ads, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 32)
  - Hoffman, Ray, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 33)
  - Huotari, Laurie, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 34)
  - Bill Ideker, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 35)
  - Individual Habilitation Plan (IHP) Schedule, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 36)
  - In-Service Training, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 37)
  - Inspections, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 38)
  - Interagency Committee, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 39)
  - Jessen, Barbara, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 40)
  - Jessen – All Staff Memos, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 41)
  - Teacher Contract Lists, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 42)
  - Job Service, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 43)
  - Kruger, Jan, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 44)
  - Legislation, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 45)
  - Licensing and Discrepancies, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 46)
  - Medicaid Inspection, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 47)
  - McKnight, Jackie, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 48)
  - Montana State Universities – Placement Services, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 49)
  - McCallum - Title I, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 50)
  - Montana Health Systems Agency, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 51)
  - Montana Consultation Services Directory, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 52)
  - Montana Foundation for Medical Care, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 53)
  - Medicaid, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 54)
  - MEA Union, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 55)
  - MPEA Union, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 56)
  - National Association of Superintendents, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 57)
  - New Dimensions, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 58)
  - Newsletters, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 59)
  - News Releases, 1982 (Box-folder 4 / 60)
  - Noonan, Nick, 1982 (Box-folder 5 / 1)
  - Page, Dianne, 1982 (Box-folder 5 / 2)
  - Porter, Charles L., 1982 (Box-folder 5 / 3)
  - Recreation Memos, 1982 (Box-folder 5 / 4)
  - Region I Developmental Disabilities (DD) Division, 1982 (Box-folder 5 / 5)
  - Residential Directory, 1982 (Box-folder 5 / 6)
  - RSUP, 1982 (Box-folder 5 / 7)
  - School Calendars, 1982 (Box-folder 5 / 8)
  - Shanley, Cindy, 1982 (Box-folder 5 / 9)
  - Governor Schinden, 1982 (Box-folder 5 / 10)
  - Scrapbook News Articles, 1982 (Box-folder 5 / 11)
  - Social and Rehabilitative Services (SRS), 1982 (Box-folder 5 / 12)
  - Surveys, 1982 (Box-folder 5 / 13)
  - Weekly Schedule, 1982 (Box-folder 5 / 14)
  - Wright and Hettringer, 1982 (Box-folder 5 / 15)
  - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box-folder 5 / 16)
  - Bacon, Ruth E., 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 17)
  - Boese, Gail M., 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 18)
  - Brooks, Richard E., 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 19)
  - Boulder River School and Hospital (BRSH), 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 20)
  - Butcher, Gerald F., 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 21)
  - Hoover, Jerry R., 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 22)
  - Butcher – All Staff Memos, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 23)
  - Calendars, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 24)
  - Copy Machine Log, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 25)
  - Christmas Program, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 26)
  - Anderson, Dan, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 27)
  - Blouke, Peter (Dr.), 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 28)
  - Gooch, Tom, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 29)
  - Haubein, Jim, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 30)
  - Moore, Don, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 31)
  - Rotering, Nick, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 32)
  - Department of Institutions, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 33)
  - South, Carroll V., 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 34)
  - Developmental Assessment Services (DAS), 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 35)
  - Developmental Disabilities (DD) Map, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 36)
  - Department of Justice, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 37)
  - Developmental Staff Correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 38)
  - Disaster Drill, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 39)
  - EPP Long Range Building Program, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 40)
  - Easter Seal Office of Public Instruction, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 41)
  - Eastern Montana Industries, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 42)
  - Eastern Subarea Advisory Council, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 43)
  - Eastmont Parents Association, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 44)
  - Fire Drills, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 45)
  - Habilitation, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 46)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 47)
  - Help Wanted, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 48)
  - In-Service to Record, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 49)
  - Inspections, 1983 (Box-folder 5 / 50)
  - Jessen, Barbara, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 1)
  - Jessen’s Memos, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 2)
  - Johnson, Carole, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 3)
  - Jones, Joyce, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 4)
  - Jones, Perry, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 5)
  - Kruger, Jan, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 6)
  - Long Term Care Survey, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 7)
  - Lyon Gary, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 8)
  - Medicaid, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 9)
  - Montana State University Placement Services, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 10)
  - MPEA Union, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 11)
  - Montana Health System Agency, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 12)
  - Monthly Population Report, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 13)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 14)
  - Nursing Home and Senior Citizen Center – State Directory, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 15)
  - Personnel Division, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 16)
  - Porter, Chuck, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 17)
  - Praric View, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 18)
  - RSUP, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 19)
  - Recreation Memos, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 20)
  - Recreation Schedules, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 21)
  - Region I – Developmental Disabilities (DD) Division, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 22)
  - Rocky Mountain Development Council, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 23)
  - Shanley, Cindy, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 24)
  - Social and Rehabilitative Services (SRS), 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 25)
  - Sivanish, Kelly, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 26)
  - Sunrise Ranch, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 27)
  - Superintendent’s Digest, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 28)
  - Surplus Property Bureau, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 29)
  - Tucker, Kathryn, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 30)
  - University of Montana, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 31)
  - Weekly Schedule, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 32)
  - Wurm, Jaci, 1983 (Box-folder 6 / 33)
  - Action for Eastern Montana, 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 34)
  - Bacon, Ruth E., 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 35)
  - Boese, Gail M., 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 36)
  - Board of Visitors, 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 37)
  - Boulder River School and Hospital (BRSH), 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 38)
  - Developmental Assessment Services (DAS), 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 39)
  - Department of Institutions, 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 40)
  - Anderson, Dan, 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 41)
  - Blouke, Peter (Dr.), 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 42)
  - Gooch, Tom, 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 43)
  - Haubien, Jim, 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 44)
  - Hoover, Jerry, 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 45)
  - South, Carroll V., 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 46)
  - Department of Health and Human Services (DPHHS), 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 47)
  - Developmental Staff, 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 48)
  - Easter Seal Society, 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 49)
  - Eastern Montana Industries, 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 50)
  - Eastmont Echo, 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 51)
  - Fire Drills, 1984 (Box-folder 6 / 52)
  - Goodell, Dave, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 1)
  - Green Thumb Incorporated, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 2)
  - House Bill 909 Advisory Council, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 3)
  - Habilitation, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 4)
  - Hammer – All Staff Memos, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 5)
  - Hammer, Sylvia, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 6)
  - Health Education Development System and Cooperative Health Education Program (HEDS/CHEP), 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 7)
  - Holm, Trish, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 8)
  - Jessen, Barbara, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 9)
  - Jessen Memos, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 10)
  - Johnson, Carole, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 11)
  - Jones, Perry, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 12)
  - Kruger, Jan, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 13)
  - Long Term Care Survey, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 14)
  - Lyon, Gary, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 15)
  - Medicaid, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 16)
  - MPEA Union, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 17)
  - MEA Union, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 18)
  - Miscellaneous Newsletters, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 19)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 20)
  - No Name Publications, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 21)
  - Porter, Chuck, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 22)
  - Recreation Schedules, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 23)
  - Recreation Memos, 1984 (Box-folder 7 / 24)